moviemart.in 2014-07-06

# Rent Movies | Buy DVD Movies Online at Lowest Price

| 

|   
---  
|    [Home](http://www.moviemart.in/index.aspx)   [Movies](http://www.moviemart.in/Movies.aspx)   [Perfumes](http://www.moviemart.in/Perfumes.aspx)   [Meditation-Accessories](http://www.moviemart.in/Meditation-Accessories.aspx)   [Todays Deals](http://www.moviemart.in/TodaysDeals.aspx)   Track Order |  | [Cart(0)](http://www.moviemart.in/Shopping_Cart.aspx?Show=cart)  
---|---|---  
|  |  |       |  |   Privacy Policy   
---  
  |  |   |  | What This Privacy Policy Covers  
---|---|---  
  |  | Information Collection and Use  
  |  | Information Sharing and Disclosurehanges  
  |  | Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences  
  |  |  Confidentiality and Security  
  |  | What Personal Information About Me Does MovieMart.in Use?  
  |  | How Secure Is The Information MovieMart.in Has About Me?  
  |  | Contact   
  
**What This Privacy Policy Cover**  
  
---  
  
This policy covers how MovieMart.in treats personal information that MovieMart.in collects and receives, including information related to your past use of MovieMart.in products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.

back to top   
  
**Information Collection and Use**  
  
MovieMart.in collects personal information when you register with MovieMart.in . When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, mailing address, zip code and phone number. Once you register with MovieMart.in , you are not anonymous to us.  
  
MovieMart.in uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

back to top  
  
**Information Sharing and Disclosure**  
  
MovieMart.in does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:  
  
We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with MovieMart.in under confidentiality agreements. MovieMart.in works with vendors, partners, advertisers, and other service providers in different industries and categories of business. These businesses such as shipping companies and credit card companies may have access to certain personal information needed to perform their functions. But these companies are under obligation not to use that information for any other purpose. By law, we sometimes must release account and other personal information when we believe release is necessary to comply with law; enforce or apply our Conditions of Use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of MovieMart.in , our users, or others. This may include exchanging information with State or Govt. officials, as well as other companies and organizations to increase fraud protection and credit risk reduction. This is for our customers' own good and protects all of us.

back to top  
  
**Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences**  
  
You can edit your (make this a hyper link) MovieMart.in Account at any time.  
  
|  | 

You can opt to receive email promotions for a specific section. This can be done at the time of registration.  
  
We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the MovieMart.in service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the MovieMart.in Newsletter, that are considered part of your MovieMart.in account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them.

back to top   
  
**Confidentiality and Security**  
  
We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.  
  
We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you.

back to top  
  
**What Personal Information About Me Does MovieMart.in Use?**  
  
Any information we learn from our customers about them helps us only to serve them better and improve their shopping experience on our site. Any information you enter on our Web site or give to us in any other way is stored securely on our servers. You may always choose not to provide certain information, but in doing so, you may deny yourself the ability to use the site or use certain features. In most cases, we use the information customers provide for such purposes as assisting with order processing, responding to your customer queries, customizing emails and shopping for customers, and simply communicating.  
  
In truth, due to our careful security measures, we receive certain types of information whenever you interact with us. Many websites, for example, use "cookies," and we do as well. These are used to recognize when you return to MovieMart.in through your browser and to follow your movements through the site to better help us in making a site that you will enjoy using. You may find some companies that offer utilities that allow you to visit sites anonymously. You are welcome to use such programs while at MovieMart.in , of course, though they will impede us from personalizing your experience on our site and may make it impossible for you to sign in and use your account.  
  
We also generally receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from MovieMart.in , though only if your computer and service provider supports such capabilities. This way, we know if, for instance, if you've received an answer to a question you may have asked, or notifications about an order you may have placed. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please change your Preferences within your account. Occasionally via email, we provide a product recommendation or special offer that we believe will interest you. Every email of this type is carefully reviewed by our staff for quality and value, as, frankly, we dislike getting "junk" email as much as anyone. Any offers you receive from us will have met specific standards and may, of course, be ignored, but we hope you find them as valuable as we do.

back to top   
  
**How Secure Is The Information MovieMart.in Has About Me?**  
  
We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software during any order transmission to encrypt valuable information customers input. Your account password is also protected, as we know how important it is to allow only authorized access to your account. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer and never give your password to anyone you aren't sure you can trust.  
  
Remember that this Privacy Policy governs your use of MovieMart.in , as well as our use of your information. It is your responsibility to review this Policy for changes, as well as your own account. If you choose to visit MovieMart.in your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Policy and our terms of usage as outlined throughout this site. This includes shipping and return policies, damage limitations, disputes, and the Indian Laws. Please check our site frequently to see any changes to this or other policies. MovieMart.in may update this policy.

back to top   
  
**Contact**  
  
Still have questions? Contact us at e-mail: [ support@moviemart.in ](mailto:support@moviemart.in)
